听译: 兰贱贱 奇迹道长
m 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0 0 0 0 0 0 b 0
4 0 9 0 13 b 4 13 9 13 13 13 b 13 9 13 4 13 0
玩具总动员
惊魂夜
校对: 人妻apple 怪查理
后期: Nico 怪查理
压制: 怪查理
'Betsy'
'Betsy.'
'不'
'No!'
小心 他就在你身后
Watch out! He's right behind you!
挡住视线了
Hey! Damn it front.
抱歉
Oh, sorry.
'我来抓你了 Betsy'
'I'm coming to get you Betsy.'
快跑啊Betsy 快跑
Run Betsy! Run!
拜托 她根本不可能逃出吸血鬼的掌心
Come on! There is no way she can outrun a vampire.
别听她的Betsy 你可以的
Don't listen to her Betsy, you can do it.
不要放弃
Don't give up.
到了吗
Are we there yet?
还有几个小时 Bonnie
No for a few more hours Bonnie.
你可以再睡一会
You can go back to sleep.
'救命 请开门'
'Help! Open the door!'
'没人能帮你了Betsy'
'No one can help you now Betsy.'
无聊
Boring.
有点耐心
Patience.
好看的恐怖片都是慢慢推进的
All great horror film starts slowly.
你看 他们设计
You see,they design...
'求你了 让我进去'
'Please, let me in!'
想办法 Betsy 快想办法
Tactics, Betsy, tactics.
找个能防卫自己的工具
Look for something to defend yourself with.
总算
There we go.
技术上来说那个一点用都没有
Oh, technically that would be useless.
所有人都知道用木棍直插心脏是杀死吸血鬼的唯一方式
Everybody knows a wooden stake through the heart is the only way to kill a vampire.
啊
Ahhh!
哈哈 一只小猫 经典的障眼法
Haha, only a kitty cat, classic misdirection.
一只猫
A cat?!
拜托 这一点都不吓人
Come on guys, this isn't scary.
救命 把我救出去
Help! Get me out of here!
Jessie 我们得把她救出来
Jessie, we have to get her out.
Jessie Jessie 能听见吗
Jessie, Jessie, can you hear me?
大家 数到三
Ok, everyone, on three.
一 二 三
One, two, three!
Jessie Jessie
Jessie? Jessie!
Jessie怎么了
What's the matter with Jessie?
她被遗弃在一只盒子里好几年
She was abandoned in a box for years.
我没法 我没法逃出去
I couldn't...I couldn't find a way out.
妈妈 我能带上我的玩具吗
Mum, can I bring my toys?
路边的汽车旅馆是恐怖片中最常见的场景之一
The roadside motel is one of the most common road cons for a horror film.
偏僻 无人 普通 给观众营造一种毫不可疑的舒心环境
Remote, isolated, ordinary, a comforting environment to a latest suspicion of audience.
我猜她马上就要向旅馆老板借电话
I expect they'll be asking the inn keeper to use the telephone any minute now.
'我能借电话用一下吗'
'Would it be ok if I use your phone?'
'我们的轮胎漏气了'
'Our car is a flat.'
时间恰好
Right on cue.
没事的Jessie 你很安全
It's ok Jessie, you'll be safe now.
很快我们就会重新上路了
We'll be back on the road before you know it.
有什么最新消息 Trixie
What's the latest, Trixie?
她还在和拖车公司通话
She's still on the phone with the tolltruck company.
'早上六点 这是你最早能到这的时间吗'
'6 a.m.? That's the earliest you can get here?'
六点
意味着我们要在这里待一晚上吗
You mean we have to stay here all night?
砰 砰 砰
Bom bom bom!
我不在乎我们在哪 只要我不独自困在那个盒子里
I don't care where we are, as long as I'm not stuck alone in that box.
请在旅客本上签字
You think you could just sign here on the guest book?
我去帮你刷卡
and I'll leave to see the major credit card for the incidentals.
让我们看看 你住七号房间吧
Ok, let's see here. I'm gonna put you in room 7.
我们这里有个说法
You know we have a little saying around here.
在好梦旅馆 好梦伴随你
At the Sleep-Well Motel, you're gonna sleep well.
看起来她们睡着了
Well, it looks like they are asleep.
终于
Finally!
Potato Head 你要去哪
Potato Head, where are you going?
我们在旅馆 我只是想看看这里的便利设施
We're at a motel, I just wanna check out the amenities.
就是免费的东西啦
You know, the free stuff.
小肥皂 浴帽 洗发露 护发素
Little soaps, shower caps, shampoo, conditioner.
我是你的话就不会出去
Oh, I wouldn't go out there if I were you.
第一个离开的总是遇到麻烦
The first leave usually gets it.
Potato Head 不要离开行李箱
Oh, Potato Head, don't leave the bag.
汽车旅馆是玩具最容易走丢的地方
A motel is one of the easiest places for a toy to get lost.
别乱担心了
Shut your worry hole.
没人会走丢的
Nobody's gonna get lost.
况且 我答应Emma要给她带点好东西回去
Besides, I promised Emma that I bring her back something nice.
等等 你们又要去哪
Wait, where are you guys going?
我们只是去看看免费的东西
We're just gonna check out the free stuff.
如果Potato Head真的遇到麻烦 我可不想错过好戏
And if something does happen to the Potato, I wouldn't want to miss it.
拜托 伙计们 待在行李箱里好吗
Oh come on guys! Let's all just stay in the bag.
Buzz 我去找那些家伙 你找Potato Head
Oh Buzz, I'll grab those guys, you get Potato head.
好的
Got it.
不 等等 不要走
No wait! Don't go!
不要担心Jessie 马上回来
Don't worry Jessie, I'll be right back!
Buzz
Buzz!
伙计们 你们在哪
Guys guys! Where are you?
Jessie 怎么了 你还好吗
Jessie, what's wrong? Are you ok?
Buzz 大伙呢
Buzz, where is everybody?
不要担心 我们都在这里
Not to worry, we're all right here.
看 Woody  Pricklepants Trixie Rex
See, there's Woody, Pricklepants, Trixie, Rex,
等等 Potato Head在哪
Wait, where is Potato head?
好戏开始
And so it begins.
Pricklepants 不要帮倒忙
Pricklepants, you're not helping.
我只是想说这种恐怖片中
I'm just saying it's quite common in these types of movies
某个毫无疑心的角色走着走着消失了很正常
for one unsuspecting character to wander off and vanish.
好吧 他不可能凭空消失
Well, he couldn't have just disappeared.
也许这地方闹鬼
Maybe this place is haunted.
什么 闹鬼
What? It's haunted?
当然不是 大家都知道世界上没有鬼
Of course not. Everybody knows ghosts aren't real.
实际上 根据我的互联网研究
Actually, according to my internet research...
不可能
Highly unlikely.
一定有一个合理的解释
There has to be a rational explanation.
我们分成两人一组
We need break into groups of two.
看好你的搭档
Everyone keep an eye on your partner.
任何异常 尖叫一声
Anything goes wrong, give a yell.
啊
Ahhh!
我踩到什么东西了
Ew, I stepped in something.
恶心
Ew!
等一下
Wait a minute.
嗯
Hmm...
这是什么
What is it?
恶心
Disgusting.
如果这里是电影 一定是在怪兽变形的时候掉下的
Were...Were this a movie, I'd say it was sliding from the creature's metamorphosis.
好吧 不管是什么
Yeah, well, whatever it is,
Potato Head踩到了
Potato Head managed to step in it,
留下了一串脚印
leaving behind a trailer of footprints,
我们跟着脚印 应该就能找到他
If we follow it, should lead us right to it.
伙计们
Hey guys!
等等 Trixie 不要
No wait! Trixie! Don't!
Trixie
Trixie!
Trixie?
Potato Head
Potato Head?
这就是黑暗之塔
And this would be the turrical.
每部电影都有
Every movie has one, you know.
一旦英雄进去 再也没有退路
Once the hero enter, there's no turning back.
Rex 赶快
Rex, hurry up!
来了
Coming!
现在我们只需找到一条下去的路
Now we just need to find a way down.
啊
Ahhh!
还真下来了
Well, that did the job.
抱歉
Sorry.
大家都还好吗
Is everyone ok?
啊
Ahh!
那里
That way.
所有人 紧靠一起
Alright everybody, stay close.
接下来会怎样
So, what happens now?
大家会被拆散 然后一个接一个被抓
Well, this would be the part where the characters get separated and then picked off one by one.
然后呢
Then what happens next?
啊
Ahhh!
Pricklepants在哪
Where is Pricklepants?
他刚刚还站在这里
He was standing right here just a moment ago.
我们要怎么办
What are we gonna do now?
他是唯一知道接下来会发生什么的人
He was the only one who knew what the heck is going on!
啊啊啊啊
Ahhhhhh!
等等 等等 听
Wait, wait, listen.
我觉得我们甩掉它了
I think we lost it.
在那
It's over there!
什么
What?
这里
Over here.
我看到了 它正在盯着我们看
I think I can see it, it's staring right at us.
是Potato Head的手臂
It's Potato Head's arm.
等一下 他貌似想告诉我们什么
Wait a minute, it looks like it's trying to tell us something.
到底是什么
What is it, little buddy?
他好像在用某种手势
I think he's using some kind of hand signals.
是数字一
It's the number one.
不 一个单词
No, one letter.
一个音节
One syllable?
很久以前
Uh, once upon a time.
一加一等于一
Uh, one plus one is one.
也许他是指上面
I think maybe it's pointing up?
- 上面  - 对
- Up! - Yeah!
当然
Of course!
把手递给我
Pass me the hand, will you?
接下来怎么办
What now?
出门 右拐
Out the door and to the right?
什么 你确定吗
What? Are you sure?
我觉得指的是左边
The hand looks like it's pointing left to me.
啊
Huh?
这边
Over here.
什么
What?
看这边
Look over here.
有人吗 有人吗
Hello? Hello?
伙计们 等一下
Hey, guys. Wait up!
Woody Buzz
Woody! Buzz!
嘘 安静士兵 你会把他们引过来的
Shhh! Quite soldier, you'll lead them right to us.
玩具在这里太危险
This place isn't safe for toys.
Combat Carl要把手移开了
Combat Carl's gonna take his hand away now.
你叫 我们都完蛋
You yell, we're done for.
明白吗
Got it?
Combat Carl经历过好多
Combat Carl's seen things,
可怕的事情
horrible things.
Combat Carl学会了永不停止
Combat Carl's learned, you gotta keep moving,
否则他们会找到你
or else they'll find you.
你是Combat Carl吗
Are you Combat Carl?
让Combat Carl坚持到现在的唯一原因
The only thing that's kept Combat Carl going is
他想也许他还能再见一次他的主人Billy
the thought he might see his owner Billy just one more time.
你最好现在就回去
You better turn back now,
否则你再也见不到你的主人
or you'll never see your owner again.
但我得找到我的朋友
But I need to find my friends.
这就是你去找你朋友的下场
This is what happens when you try to find your friends.
嘘 听到了吗
Shhh. Did you hear that?
他找到我们了 我们被困住了
He found us, we are trapped.
不 Combat Carl从不放弃
No, Combat Carl never gives up,
Combat Carl总能想到办法
Combat Carl finds a way.
我们得走了 准备好了吗
We gotta move. You ready?
什么 不
What? No!
数到三
We're going on three.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
抓紧我
Grab my arm.
Carl 等等 Carl
Carl, wait, Carl!
不要管Combat Carl 快逃
Forget about Combat Carl, just go!
啊
Ahhhh!
喂
Hey!
放开我 你这个大坏蛋
Let me go! You big vomit!
立刻放开我
Let me go instant!
谢谢 很有趣
Thank you, well, it's been fun.
麻烦来了
看起来挺旧的 应该值点钱
Hmm, looks old, probably worth something.
干得好 Mr. Jones
Excellent find, Mr. Jones.
他走了
He's gone.
安全
All clear.
Jessie
Jessie!
Buzz
Buzz！
你没事真是太好了
I'm so glad you're safe.
牛仔女 你总算安然无恙地找到这里 真是不错
Nice to see you made it here in one piece, cowgirl.
Carl
Carl!
让我来给你介绍一下
Combat Carl would like to introduce you
Combat Carl三分之一大小模型 小Combat Carl
to his one third skill counterpart, Combat Carl Junior.
小姐 抱歉打扰了你欢聚的喜悦 我们现在时间紧张
Ma'am sorry to break up the party, but we're on a tight schedule.
Pocketeer 到你上了
Pocketeer, you're up!
口袋出击
Pockets away!
乐高兔子 上
Lego bunny, go!
有看到那个人或者那只蜥蜴吗
Any sign of our guy or the lizard?
没有 这里仍然安全
No sir. Area is still clear.
老时钟
Hey, old timer.
时间来得及吗
How we doing.
让我看看
Well, sir.
他已经离开了19秒
He's been gone for nineteen seconds.
经理Ron随时都可能回来
Ron the manager could come back any minute.
好 就让我再试一试
OK, let's try this again.
第三次一定能成功
Third time's the charm.
你办得到
You can do it, Junior.
稳住 别紧张
Steady. Take it easy now.
差一点就成功了
Almost got it！
哦不
Oh-no!
糟糕
Sassafras!
那是最后一个了
That was the last one!
意味着 我是 下一个
That means, I'm next!
你们看不到吗 我是牢固四侠的最后一个
Don't you see, I'm the last of the Fastener Four.
看 先是Zipper man 再是Snaps 然后是Speed lacer
Look, Zipper man! Snaps! Speed lacer!
我是下一个
I'm next!
下一个就是我
我是
I'm...
冷静下来 伙计
Keep it together man!
我们会找到出路的
We will find a way out!
我们是会找到出路的 装在盒子里罢了
We will get out all right, in boxes.
啥
What!
Jessie 没人会被装进盒子里
Jessie, nobody is getting boxed up.
我们会一起离开的
We're leaving together.
您有一笔销售
You have a sale.
Pez cat 你看到什么了
Pez cat, what do you see!
啊呜 看不太清诶
Ah-u, it's hard to make out.
不过看起来像是一个 牛仔
But it looks like a cowboy.
我们看看下一个卖掉的是什么
let's see what's next to go.
什么 2000块
What! 2000 dollars!
吼吼吼 Jones Jones
Hohoho, Jones Jones.
你不会相信的
You're not gonna believe this.
旅途愉快 牛仔Andy
Happy trails, cowboy Andy.
就像抢婴儿的糖果一样容易
Like taking candy from a baby.
他会想办法逃出来的 Woody
He'll be able to get out, Woody.
我也不知道
I have no foggist idea.
一开始就是个经典的恐怖电影 结果变成了悲剧
What starts out is a classic horror film has turned into something more of a tragedy.
我不敢相信 我们将再也见不到Bonnie了
I can't believe we're never gonna see Bonnie again.
Combat Carl想再见一次Billy
Combat Carl would have liked to see Billy just one more time.
Carl 我们会找到办法的
We'll find a way, Carl.
会找到办法的
We'll find a way.
战士们 你们最好快点
Hey, you better hurry Soldier.
听起来 修理人员随时可能出现哦
Sound fixing arrives in any minute now.
您有一笔销售
You have a sale.
大家快回到原位
People, back to your position.
好极了 来了 大生意
All right. Come on, Big money.
这次轮到谁了
Who is it this time?
好 我来看看 我在看
OK, I'm looking, I'm looking.
天啊 他站起来了
Oh my god, he's getting up.
Jonesy Jonesy 我们找到另一个大金矿了
Jonesy, Jonesy, we got another gold mine.
看起来 该你上路了
Looks like you get to go on a little trip.
是你给加油站打电话 说有轮胎要修理的吧
Yeah, you got a gas for the flat-tire that needs fixing.
是的 我带你去
Absolutely. Come on, I'll show you the way.
好了 他走了
OK, he's gone!
没用的 我不够高
It's no use. I'm not tall enough.
我去找Woody
I'll go get Woody.
我们一起就可以够得着把手了
Together we will be able to reach the handle.
好计划 Jessie
Good plan, Jessie.
有人到门口了
Ahh! Someone's at the door.
放在那里 柜台上的都送走
Stack there, and the ones on the counter all go too.
好的
OKAY.
看来我得跑两趟了
Looks I'm gonna have to take two trips.
Woody
Ah Woody!
好吧 我们需要B计划
Alright, we need a plan B.
大家都想想
Put on your thinking caps, people.
我想到了
I got it.
她可以闯进送货车里
She can make a break through the delivery truck.
这可行不通
It's what daylight.
况且 她也赶不上啊
Besides, she will never make it in time.
我该怎么办
What do I do?
现在我们都将会被关进盒子里
Now, we're all gonna end up in a box.
等等 这就对了
Wait, that's it.
Jessie 再说一遍
Jessie say that again.
说什么
Say what?
说我们最终都会被关进盒子里
That we're all gonna end up in boxes?
不是我们 是你
Not us, you.
你要进到盒子里
You're gonna get in the box.
什么
What?
几分钟后 那个运货小姐就回来拿剩下的几个盒子
Listen, in a few minutes, the delivery lady is gonna come back through that door and take the other boxes.
你就混在其中
And you are gonna be in one of them.
这是你救Woody唯一的办法
It's the only way to free Woody.
不行 我不行 我办不到
No, no way. I can't. I can't do that.
我不能进到盒子里 我不能
I can't get in a box. I can't!
一定有其他的办法
There's gotta be another way.
这是唯一的办法
This is the way.
你得振作起来 战士
You better snap out of it, soilder.
我们现在时间紧迫 你是我们唯一的希望
We're running out of time. And you are the only chance we've got.
不 我不行的
No! I can't.
Jessie 听我说 想想你的特训
Jessie, Listen to me. Remember your training.
但是我没特训过
But I don't have any training.
啥 那算了
What, forget about that!
当Combat Carl遭遇危机  他对自己说
When Combat Carl get stuck in a jam, he says to himself:
Combat Carl永不放弃
Combat Carl never gives up!
Combat Carl能想到办法
Combat Carl finds a way!
现在跟我说
Now say it!
Combat Carl永不放弃
Combat Carl never gives up!
你不是Combat Carl
You're not Combat Carl!
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想到办法
Jessie finds a way!
我听不见
I can't hear you.
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想到办法
Jessie finds a way!
耶
Yeah!
还有一件事
One more thing!
小声点
Keep it down.
好吧
I'll try.
醒醒 你自由了
Wake up, you're free.
谁敢召唤Transtron
Who dares summon Transtron?
我要用这个盒子
I need to use this box.
Transtron自由了
Transtron free?
是 过来 帮我个忙
Yes, right here, give me your hand.
我怎么报答你呢
Er...How can I ever repay you?
把我封起来
Seal me in.
额
Er.
好
OK.
到你了
You're up.
Ok
Ok.
等等 停手 别封住
Wait, wait, don't tape it.
这样我就出不来了
I won't be able to get out.
关上盒子 把那个盒子放在我上面 堆起来就好
Just close the flaps and put that box on the top of it, it'll give it shut.
你确定
Are you sure about this?
不 不确定
No. Not really.
我们星球的神灵一定会让你永垂不朽的
My globe tron's ghost you shall be remembered,
好吧
All right.
变身 分离
Put the tron. Seperate.
还有其他人
Anything else?
计划貌似有效
Well, the plan seems to be working.
到目前为止都很好
So far so good.
又忘记封盒子了
Oh forgot to tape again.
什么 不 不
What! No no.
她被封住了
She got sealed in.
没戏了 我们永远都出不去了
That's it. We're never gonna get out of here.
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想到办法
Jessie finds a way!
问题解决 您随时可走
You're good to go.
太谢谢了
Thank you so much.
Bonnie 你的包包别忘了 我们马上就要走了
Don't forget your bag Bonnie. We're leaving in two minutes.
不好意思 借过
Excuse me, coming through.
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想到办法
Jessie finds a way!
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想到办法
Jessie finds a way!
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想到办法
Jessie finds a way!
Jessie永不放弃
Jessie never gives up!
Jessie能想法办法
Jessie finds a way!
Jessie想到办法了
Woody Woody
Woody? Woody?
Jessie Jessie 我在这里
Jessie, Jessie, over here.
都过去好一会了
It's been a while.
我想她回不来了
I don't think she's coming back.
耐心点 电影里不是总说 计谋成功总是欲扬先抑
Patience. Cinematics strategetic always duck.
焦躁小短裤 生活不是电影 他们不会再回来了
Panic pants, life ain't a movie, they're never coming back.
看 他们回来了
Look, they are coming back.
要退房吗 希望你在这里过得不错
Checking out? Hope you enjoy your stay.
的确不错 谢谢
We did, thanks.
Jessie 我们走
Come on Jessie, let's move.
妈妈 我们要去外婆家了吗
Mama, are we going to Grandma's now?
马上就走 宝贝儿
Any minute, honey.
Bonnie
Bonnie.
好 现在站在我肩上 然后我
OK now, climb on my shoulders and then...
Jessie Jessie
Jessie, Jessie.
天啊 她在做什么
God, what is she doing?
她直冲向门帘了
She's heading straight for the curtain.
这不是计划的一部分啊
That's not part of the plan.
Jessie
Jessie.
加油
Come on.
我的手
My hand.
看 我早告诉过你吧
See, told you.
好啊
Perfect.
我看不下去了
I can't look.
来抓我啊
Come and get it.
感谢您与好梦旅馆共度美好时光
Thanks for staying with us, this is the Sleep-Well.
我的玩具诶
My toys.
不不不 小女孩
No no no, little girl.
那个区域只能员工进入
That area is for employees only.
嘿
Hey!
我不能让你待在这儿
I can't have you back here.
那些都是我女儿的玩具吗
Are those my daughter's toys?
Jessie
Jessie.
这些 可能是她的
Those are... they might be hers.
只是个误会而已
It's just a mistake.
知道吗 我应该报警
You know I really should call the police.
报警 没必要牵涉到警方
The police? Come on, there's no need to involve the authority.
走吧 Bonnie 我们走了
Come on, Bonnie, let's go, we're leaving.
你不考虑卖掉它们吗
Would you consider selling them, tell you what.
牛仔我出100块
I'll give you 100 dollars for the cowboy.
你要多少 200
What do you want? 200?
结局了 我们又回到了起点
The epilog! We're back to the location where it all began.
从没想过我会想念后车厢
Never thought I'd miss the trunk.
你做到了 Jessie 你拯救了大家
You did it. Jessie, you saved us all.
Jessie没放弃
Jessie didn't give up!
Jessie想到了办法
Jessie found a way!
好吧 Woody想说的是 谢谢
Well, Woody wants to say, thanks.
Potato head 你们看到Potato head吗
Potato head, have you seen Potato head?
啥 不
What, no.
天啊 看来怪物转身回来夺走最终的受害者
Oh, dear. It seems the monster has returned to claim one final victim.
他好着呢 在那儿呢
No, he hasn't. He's right over there.
你回来真是太好了 宝贝儿
Oh, I'm so glad to have you back, baby.
我们以后再也不分离
We are never gonna get saperated again.
真是的
Ahh, nuts.
大家欢声笑语 我得说阴霾已经离去 电影也该结束了
Group laughter, I shall say now the worst is behind us and the movie is just about to over.
这就结束了
So, this is the ending?
是的 我说 都到了出演员表的时候
Yes, I'd say everyone in the credits about now.
运输车到了
Transport has arrived.
听到猫咪发话了 我们走
You heard the cat, let's move.
谢谢你 伙计
Thanks buddy.
下一站 Billy的家
Next stop, Billy's house.
Jones
Mr.Jones!
给你 伙计
Here you go, buddy.
欢迎来到好梦旅馆 有什么我能
Welcome to the Sleep-Well, How may I...
你是这里的经理吗
Are you the manager?
我 不 我不是
Me? No, I'm not the manager.
那啥 我去叫他来
I'll tell you what. I'll go get him for you.
早就告诉过你 不要把钥匙留在车里
Told you not to leave the keys in the car.
嫌犯逃跑
We got a runner.
电波字幕组 欢迎您的加入官方网站:www.dbfansub.com
新浪微博:@电波字幕组